(CHEERING)
THANK YOU
♪♪♪
♪ WHERE IT BEGAN I CAN'T
BEGIN TO KNOWING ♪
♪ BUT THEN I KNOW
IT'S GROWING STRONG ♪
♪ WAS IN THE SPRING ♪
♪ THEN SPRING
BECAME THE SUMMER ♪
♪ WHO'D HAVE BELIEVED
YOU'D COME ALONG ♪
♪ HANDS TOUCHING HANDS ♪
♪ REACHING OUT TOUCHING
ME TOUCHING YOU ♪
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN INCLINED ♪
♪ TO BELIEVE THEY NEVER WOULD ♪
♪ BUT NOW I ♪
♪ LOOK AT THE NIGHT AND
IT DON'T SEEM SO LONELY ♪
♪ WE FILL IT UP WITH ONLY TWO ♪
♪ AND WHEN I HURT ♪
♪ HURTING RUNS OFF
MY SHOULDERS ♪
♪ HOW CAN I HURT WHEN
I'M HOLDING YOU ♪
♪ ONE TOUCHING ONE ♪
♪ REACHING OUT TOUCHING
ME TOUCHING YOU ♪
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN INCLINED ♪
♪ TO BELIEVE THEY NEVER WOULD ♪
♪ OH NO NO ♪
ALL RIGHT WE'RE COMING UP
TO THE LAST CHORUS NOW
I'M GONNA NEED TO HEAR
EVERYBODY SINGING FOLKS
COME ON TAKE A DEEP BREATH
WE'LL DO IT TOGETHER
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN INCLINED ♪
♪ TO BELIEVE THEY NEVER WOULD ♪
COME ON WE'RE TAKING
IT UP A HALF-STEP
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN INCLINED ♪
♪ TO BELIEVE THEY NEVER WOULD ♪
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
♪ ♪
(CHEERING)
THANK YOU SO MUCH
COME ON RONNIE
♪ HANDS TOUCHING HANDS ♪
♪ REACHING OUT TOUCHING
ME TOUCHING YOU ♪
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN INCLINED ♪
♪ TO BELIEVE THEY NEVER WOULD ♪
LAST CHORUS
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD SO GOOD ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN INCLINED ♪
♪ TO BELIEVE THEY NEVER WOULD ♪
♪ SWEET CAROLINE ♪
OH YES OH YES
♪♪♪
(CHEERING)